# SUSAN RENAUD

UX RESEARCHER

# PROGRAMMING/UX EXPERIENCE

## Le Wagon London Coding Bootcamp

July 2019 - Sep 2019

 9-week intensive full-stack coding bootcamp learning UX/UI, UX Research, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6,SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku, Ruby on Rails.

# Projects:

**Two-Wheeler** - Collaborated with another developer to design and implement a bike rental platform using Ruby on Rails.

• **Losty!** - In a group of two people, designed using Ruby on Rails, a fully functional lost and found web application where people who lose things can connect to those who have found them.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Applied Behavior Learning Center**

Apr 2016 - Oct 2018

Team Lead Behavioral Therapist

- Implemented Applied Behavior Analysis techniques in 1:1 therapy sessions to children ages 2-13 diagnosed with Autism Spectrum Disorders.
- Performed client-specific programs and protocols intended to build a variety of skills. These include self help skills, communication and social skills, emotional regulation and attending, and decrease targeted challenging behaviors.
- Managed client records, data and materials; responsible for making sure behavioral therapists on clients' teams implemented programming correctly.
- Collected, graphed and managed various types of client data.

## Frankino Lab - University of Houston

May 2013 - Dec 2015

# Lab Manager

- Conducted an original experiment testing whether the flight ability of Drosophila melanogaster affects survival in the presence of a predator, and whether effects hold across different temperatures.
- Organized day to day lab labor including maintenance of stocks and implementation of experiments.
- Trained lab members in lab protocols, best practices, and experiment implementation procedures.
- Arranged and managed work schedules for up to eight student workers.

# **BOUNCE (Behavior Opportunities Uniting Counseling** Aug 2015 - Dec 2015 and Education)

## Intern

- Collaborated with group members to administer nutrition/healthy lifestyle classes at elementary schools to girls aged 9-14.
- Assisted with administering surveys, data collection, data entry, and data management including use of Qualtrics and Excel.

### EDUCATION

#### University of Houston

Dec 2015

Bachelor of Science in Psychology and Public Health Magna Cum Laude



### SUMMARY

I am a tech-savvy UX Researcher looking to utilize my newly acquired programming skills while leveraging my previous experience. I chose to study psychology and public health in university because I wanted to make a positive impact on the world. This passion along with my interest in research and data analytics led me to work in Applied Behavior Analysis where my latent interest in technology steadily grew. After nearly three years, that interest became fully realized, and I knew I needed a change. After taking some time off, I decided to attend Le Wagon London Bootcamp to learn full-stack web development. I am confident that the skills I gained there will help me have a bigger impact on an increasingly digital world.

## SKILLSET

- Web Development
  - Ruby
  - Ruby on Rails
  - HTML
  - o CSS/SCSS
  - Javascript(ES6)
  - Databases
  - SQL
  - UX/UI
  - UX Research
- Management/Team Leadership
- Research
- Applied Behavior Analysis

#### CONTACT



1-832-260-4278



serenaud89@gmail.com



susan-renaud.com



susan-renaud



susanelizabethrenaud